Where are the secretaries?
(Where are the secretaries?)
(I can't ask my manager to do something like this.)
(But I can ask my secretary.)
(Don't secretaries usually handle more discreet matters?)
(A secretary is someone who stays by your side...)
(and shares even your most closely guarded secrets.)
A secretary is...
How many people in Korea have their own secretaries?
Let's be real.
Unless you're a CEO, you don't get to have your own secretary.
(They've returned with the dignity of true secretaries.)
That's why you can't get used to it.
(My gosh)
You startled me.
It's hot. Stay away from me.
(Sticking together)
Hey. I'm only sticking with you...
- because the producer told me to.
- It's hot.
(Season 2 opens with an adorable shot of the 2 together.)
Do you like your partner?
What if I don't?
Will you replace him?
(Dimples coming out)
(He senses his job is in danger.)
So...
What do you think?
Me?
(Suddenly polite)
- Why did you suddenly get polite?
- No.
- Well...
- Why?
I've done everything on this show.
I drank sundae soup in a car.
(I drank sundae soup in a car.)
I put contact lenses in someone's eyes.
(I put contact lenses in someone's eyes.)
(My Star is satisfied.)
I filmed a challenge.
I hosted the pre-concert segment.
(I hosted the pre-concert segment.)
(I gave acting advice.)
(I put nail tips on someone's fingernails.)
I even sang.
If you're curious, why don't you come and experience it yourself?
I, Lee Seo Jin,
will do anything for you.
Can you say your last line again?
Say, "If you're curious, come to our show as My Star."
That's basically like begging.
Gosh, that's annoying.
That's the most annoying thing in the world.
(It hurts his pride.)
But you're determined, aren't you?
"Determined?"
I said I'd take care of them.
Isn't that enough?
So just come and see it yourself.
If you're curious, come on the show.
If you aren't, just forget it.
(My Genie Secretary warmly welcomes My Stars.)
(Clearing his throat)
I heard some unsettling rumors recently.
There's been a lot of talk...
that either Kwang Soo or Kwang Hee might be coming.
Who else could handle that fussy young master?
That's me.
No one else can do it.
He's only doing so well...
because I've been there supporting him all along.
Seo Jin was...
(Laughing)
Seo Jin was... No. Seo Jin...
Seo Jin...
Hey, close the door.
(He even makes the young master laugh.)
Genie will do anything for you.
Do you think you can do this without me?
I'll do anything for you!
(Grander)
(More meticulous)
(Secretaries are ready to pour their hearts into the job.)
I'm so tired.
(If My Star wants something, )
(they'll do anything to make it happen.)
(The one and only pair of Genies...)
(who can make your wishes come true)
Genie will do anything for you. My Genie Secretary.
(Genie Will Do Anything for You, My Genie Secretary)
(The secretaries who will do anything for My Star have come...)
(to the hottest festival in Korea right now.)
(Waterbomb Festival 2026)
(The combination of water and music will beat the heat.)
(The 2026 Waterbomb Festival drew a cumulative audience of 830,000.)
(As of 2025, the festival was held in 13 cities around the world.)
(Right in the heart of youth, )
(where streams of water rain down on artists as they take the stage)
I'm a top-tier marksman.
(A 60-year-old secretary came to the Waterbomb Festival.)
What's the concept for today's outfit?
The Waterbomb Festival.
(A very simple outfit of the day)
It's "water."
(Wearing a knit shirt under the scorching sun)
But what does "bomb" mean?
(What does "bomb" mean in "Waterbomb?")
What do you think Seo Jin will wear?
I think he might wear shorts.
Today, he'll be wearing shorts...
a short-sleeved shirt,
a thin necklace,
and two thin bracelets on his right wrist.
- Here he is.
- Yes.
(Seo Genie came at the perfect time.)
(Loading his water gun)
(Sliding)
Gosh.
My prediction was right.
(A thin necklace and bracelet, a short-sleeved shirt, and shorts)
(He correctly guessed what Seo Jin would wear to the festival.)
(He fearlessly sprays him with a water gun.)
Stop it.
(Scared)
(The lovebugs are overflowing with affection from the start.)
(Glancing)
You're wearing shorts.
You can't wear shorts when you work.
Do you think your outfit is okay?
Hey. This is for the Waterbomb Festival. The blue moon.
What does it have to do with the Waterbomb Festival?
(Barking)
- Hey.
- What? Even the dog is barking.
That darn dog...
- Hey.
- Yes?
- "Water" means water.
- Yes.
What does "bomb" mean?
Bomb.
You're a former Army sergeant. How do you not know that?
(So "bomb" doesn't mean night?)
So "bomb" means bomb?
Everyone is holding a water gun.
- Hey.
- I think...
this is a restricted military area.
- Is that so?
- Everyone has a gun.
- Well...
- What?
I'll show off my bayonet-fighting skills today.
- You brought a gun too.
- I brought my gun.
I prepared it for BIBI.
Did you look into her?
Yesterday, I watched YouTube...
- all night.
- Okay.
- Let me tell you about BIBI.
- Go on.
Her most widely known song is "Yeon Yang Gang."
- It's "Bam Yang Gang." - "Bam Yang Gang."
Are you hungry again?
- Have you not eaten?
- No, I haven't.
- My gosh.
- I had a bit of chicken porridge.
"Yeon Yang Gang?" What was that?
(Making her 5th appearance at the Waterbomb Festival this year, )
(she's the original Waterbomb Queen.)
(From "Bam Yang Gang," which took Korea by storm, )
(to "BIBI Vengeance," which has racked up over 100 million views)
("10th on Billboard's '20 Best K-pop Songs of 2024'")
("From Number 1 Korea to Billboard")
(She's a global star who made it into the Billboard charts.)
Hello, I'm Kim Hyeong Seo.
(She won the Excellence Award at the SBS Drama Awards...)
(for her role in "The Fiery Priest 2.")
(Today's My Star transcends genres, from music to acting.)
Hello.
(My Star in the meantime)
Hi.
That was nice.
(She's already busy before the show even starts.)
(See you soon, secretaries.)
- Let's go.
- Yes.
- The artist will be arriving soon.
- Yes. Let's go.
(They hurry over to meet My Star.)
Where should we go?
We're supposed to get through all those people?
There's only one way.
(Crowded)
(The entrance is packed with young people from all over the country.)
(There are just too many people.)
Kwang Kyu, bring the gun.
Yes, sir.
(The first schedule: Meet the Waterbomb Queen)
Load your gun.
- It's loaded.
- What?
It's loaded.
- Oh, my gosh.
- My goodness.
It's My Genie Secretary.
(People recognize them as they approach the entrance.)
(Shy and happy)
- Oh, my.
- It's cold.
- Hi! How are you?
- I know you!
(Even an international attendee recognized him.)
- Oh, my.
- Hi.
- I know you!
- How are you?
Thank you, and you?
I can speak English today.
You just said, "Fine, thank you."
(The energy of the young crowd gets them all excited.)
- It's hot.
A nice, cold draft beer would be...
(I want a nice, cold draft beer.)
(It felt like 42°C on the day of filming.)
(Safey Advisory: Extreme heat is expected to continue.)
It's so hot.
(A woman in a crop top)
(Half-naked men)
I guess everyone is wearing swimwear here.
(Swimwear everywhere)
(A special Waterbomb Festival dress code made for the summer heat)
(Some people are shirtless.)
(Bundled up)
(Wait. That's what we're supposed to wear here?)
I looked around.
No one was dressed like us.
I was shocked.
Everyone was shirtless, but I couldn't take off my shirt.
I used to be fit.
It's not unusual...
to walk around in swimwear in the States.
I guess Korea is being more open-minded too.
The culture seems to have changed a lot.
(They're strolling around, pretending everything is fine.)
(But you can tell he's flustered by looking at his pouty lips.)
(The water cannons fire.)
(The blast of water sends their excitement through the roof.)
(Startled)
(They even fire the water cannons?)
"What's going on?"
"Is this how young people play these days?"
When we were little, all we did was play with water using plastic bowls.
It was surprising.
I didn't know it was that big of a festival.
(We didn't play like this.)
(What's that?)
(A whole new discovery)
(There's a giant water gun that people can actually fire.)
(Interested)
(He goes straight to it.)
So you can fire this?
(A blast of water)
(He got soaked trying out the new technology.)
(This is fun.)
(Going back)
(One more time)
(Cheering)
(He quickly adapts to the new technology.)
(Satisfied)
(Should I try firing the water gun too?)
(Kwang Kyu is firing the gun.)
(Let's play together, secretaries.)
(Young people's culture is pretty fascinating.)
Did someone shoot a water gun at us?
- What?
- Did someone shoot us?
It's the water you shot.
- It came back to me?
- Because of the wind.
(Gosh, I'm completely soaked.)
Is this the waiting room?
(Meanwhile, today's My Star...)
(is waiting for the secretaries.)
(My Star, BIBI)
- BIBI is...
- Oh, gosh.
(Lee Gyu Rim, BIBI's manager)
(Looking around)
- Why is it so hot in here?
- Did you turn on the fan?
What's this place for?
(They're going to meet My Star now.)
(5 seconds before meeting My Star)
Hello.
Is that BIBI? No, she's not. Or is she?
- Is that BIBI?
- BIBI.
(They didn't recognize her because...)
(of the backlighting and their aging eyes.)
(Blurry vision)
- She is.
- She is?
Hello.
It's BIBI.
- Is she?
- Yes.
Is that BIBI? Is that so?
(He messed up. He didn't recognize My Star.)
(Oh, hello.)
(Oh, My Star.)
It was the backlighting. We couldn't really see your face.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- Hello.
(They warmly greet each other, but...)
(Could it be because things got off on the wrong foot?)
- It's nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
(Cheering)
(It looks delicious.)
(Don't eat something like that!)
(Why are you telling me what to do?)
(Strict Secretary 1 doesn't cut her any slack.)
(Where is Kwang Kyu?)
(Oh, it's someone else's waiting room.)
(Gosh, this is frustrating!)
(You make me so tired.)
(Absent-minded Secretary 2 is in for a serious scolding.)
(A tear-soaked day for My Star and the middle-aged secretaries)
Why were you sitting here?
It was cold inside.
- It was cold?
- It was cold over there.
It was cold.
We're so hot.
- It was cold for me.
- Then...
- shall we sit here?
- Yes.
How about this table?
(It's hot for them, but they sit outside for My Star.)
- Take a seat.
- Okay.
You're very tall.
- Yes. People often tell me...
- Right?
- I'm taller than they expected.
- Oh, my.
- You're quite tall.
- Are you 168cm?
Yes, I'm 168cm.
How did you know?
(A big reaction)
I got it right.
(Her reaction makes him feel proud.)
He's happy.
(My Star has big reactions.)
(They took a seat, but...)
(Looking around awkwardly)
(Fumbling awkwardly)
- Then...
- It feels different.
What feels different?
It's different from how you looked in the drama with all that makeup.
(In "The Fiery Priest 2")
- Right.
- I watched the drama yesterday.
- I see.
- Yes.
(Actually...)
(From hard-hitting action...)
(and heart-wrenching tearjerkers...)
(to hilarious comedy where she even gets to smack other actors, )
(she's a versatile actress who can do it all.)
You look different from how you did in the drama.
(He tries to break the ice by talking about her acting.)
I'm a big fan of the show produced by Na Yeong Seok.
You've met him, haven't you?
- I've seen your shows.
- Yes.
So it feels like I know you so well.
I've seen both of you so much on TV shows.
(My Star and the secretaries can relate to each other a lot.)
What's this? This is so uncomfortable.
Is this a cushion designed for hemorrhoids or something?
(My Star feels uncomfortable because of the chair.)
- Turn slightly to the side.
- Like this?
(A useful tip)
It'd be better if you turned the chair slightly.
- Turn the chair?
- Like this.
- Should I turn the chair?
- Yes.
- You can rest your arm like that.
- How is it?
- It's nice.
- I knew it.
- I can rest my arm like this too.
I did it.
(I think I'll do a great job looking after her today.)
(His thoughtful attentiveness has won her over.)
First off, this is my manager.
Nice to meet you. I'm Lee Gyu Rim.
Hello.
This is a transition document.
(Handing over the transition document)
(He hasn't had a handover in 7 months.)
We're not going anywhere else today.
(My Star's schedule)
(2:35pm, An eyewear brand booth event)
(2:55pm, A shampoo brand booth event)
(There are many events and photoshoots as well.)
(It's packed with various events.)
You've been to the Waterbomb Festival a lot, right?
One, two, three, four...
This is my fourth time.
- Fourth?
- Yes.
(Since 2022)
(My Star's performed at the Waterbomb Festival every year.)
I've been coming here every year.
How many songs are you going to sing today?
- Sorry? Maybe 7?
- How many songs? 4?
- Seven.
- Seven?
Yes.
(Seven songs on a hot day like this?)
Can you do that while getting drenched?
Your face looks so much smaller in person than it does on screen.
Thank you.
Are you going to sing "The Weekend" today?
- "The Weekend?" - That's the first song.
What's "The Weekend?"
How high did that song chart on Billboard?
- It peaked at number 29...
- Okay.
- on the Radio Songs.
- In...
- the States?
- In the States.
In the American radio chart?
- Were the lyrics in English?
- Yes.
Is your most-viewed music video...
"BIBI Vengeance," with over 100 million views?
Right. It's "BIBI Vengeance."
Does it have more views than "Bam Yang Gang?"
- Right.
- In the other countries.
In Korea, "Bam Yang Gang" was a massive hit.
But "BIBI Vengeance..."
- was my biggest international hit.
- Are there any swear words...
in the lyrics?
The Korean title is "Bad X." Is "X" a B-word?
- What is "X?" - It is a B-word.
(Like this?)
That's right.
(He proudly sang along to the lyrics he memorized.)
I listened to the song yesterday.
Actually, out of all the songs I'm going to perform today,
"Bam Yang Gang" is pretty much the only song you can play on TV.
You're the only one who didn't know the song. He didn't know the song.
- He didn't know "Bam Yang Gang?" - He didn't know the song.
(He didn't know "Bam Yang Gang?")
I knew it.
But he didn't know.
You're the only one who didn't know the song. He didn't know the song.
(Why would you say that?)
(He heard the song for the first time while learning about her.)
(Looking at her nervously)
My gosh. He didn't know the song.
Did you deliberately try to avoid listening to it?
"Oh, it's 'Bam Yang Gang!' I'm not going to listen to it!"
It was played so much. I can't believe you've never heard it...
unless you deliberately tried to avoid it.
That's not it.
I don't know many songs.
I don't know many artists or songs.
Don't you listen to the radio while driving?
I don't listen to Korean music.
(You're doomed.)
What?
(His excuse only made things worse.)
- He's quite annoying.
- He's annoying.
I definitely got that impression.
(Annoying)
I mean...
when I was a student,
they only played English songs on the radio.
They didn't play Korean music.
- What are you talking about?
- But...
- it's 2026 now.
- So...
I'm stuck in the past.
You're stuck in the past?
- Right.
- Some people are like that.
I don't listen to modern English songs.
I listen to old ones.
I don't know new songs.
Like what?
Old ones.
(My Star is trying to relate to him.)
We're from the same generation, but I only listen to Korean music.
("Reality," the soundtrack from the movie "La Boum")
Yes. Do you know this song?
(The middle-aged man is happy.)
It goes like this, right?
- Sophie Marceau?
- Yes.
You kind of remind me of her.
You kind of look like her.
I don't think so.
- No. I see the resemblance.
- That's...
No.
(Annoying)
Who do you think she looks like then?
(He ruined my mood.)
(He needs to do something to leave a better impression.)
Talk wisely.
If I had to compare you to a Western singer...
I'd say you give off a Christina Aguilera vibe.
- I love her.
- You give off a Christina vibe.
(Not annoying)
This is fun.
Why am I having so much fun?
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Aren't you from Busan?
I'm from Changwon.
- I'm sorry.
- You messed up.
But I read online that you're from Busan.
I was born in Busan...
- and went to college there.
- You went to college there.
My parents are from Busan.
My family has been from Busan for generations.
I'm so happy to meet you. We're from the same city.
- I'll speak to you casually now.
- Sure.
- Gosh.
- I don't mind.
If there's anything you want us to do, don't hesitate to ask.
- Okay.
- Today...
Even if you had a daughter, she'd still be older than her.
- Right.
- Do you have a son?
- What?
(He's 58 and single.)
No, he doesn't.
He's not married.
But he's old. I bet he's older than your father.
My father was born in 1968.
So I was right. He's one year older than your father.
- I told you.
- My goodness.
Oh, my gosh.
You look a lot younger than your age.
You haven't changed at all.
(Would she be okay with being looked after by an old man?)
(He checks her schedule again.)
- There are some events.
- Yes.
Before the show,
I'm going to attend some events.
- Two events.
- Yes.
But there'll be people...
on the way to the booth.
You're so pretty!
(The original Waterbomb Queen draws a crowd wherever she goes.)
(They'll act as her bodyguards for safety.)
Please take good care of her.
It'd be great if you could distract people.
There's an eyewear brand booth event?
Yes. It's the eyewear brand she endorses.
- Yes.
- It's an eyewear brand.
- She's the brand ambassador.
- Yes.
There's a shampoo brand event too?
- Shampoo...
- I don't endorse the brand,
but I'd love to.
Please put in a good word for me with the people in charge.
But I'd love to.
(My Star is hoping to land a shampoo commercial.)
- Shampoo?
- Yes.
- What shampoo is that?
- It's because...
It's because I actually use...
a lot of Head and Shoulders products.
(Head and shoulder?)
Do you have dandruff?
(Do you have dandruff?)
(How could you ask such a question to My Star?)
Do you have dandruff?
Yes. It's quite serious. My grandfather had dandruff.
So it's really bad.
- My scalp is dry.
- It's dry.
- Your scalp?
- Yes.
- Right.
- Rash?
- Yes.
- When she also...
dyes her hair...
- It becomes dry.
- Yes.
You can't wear black clothes.
Yes. So I try not to wear them.
When I do, I don't shake my head.
I keep it still.
You know about this, right? Didn't you wear...
- black uniforms?
- I did.
Kids used to have a lot of dandruff...
- on their shoulders.
- So much.
Back in our day, we even had lice.
You also had lice? When...
Are you talking about the Korean War times?
(Now that he's grown up, it's become a place where lice can't survive.)
At the previous Waterbomb Festival,
the string on her bikini top came loose.
(At the previous Waterbomb Festival)
It was a frightening moment.
(While changing her outfit on stage)
(The bikini string came loose.)
(BIBI's bikini top comes undone during her Waterbomb performance.)
(Thanks to her manager's quick response, )
(she was able to finish the performance well.)
We can notice that,
but we can't tie it for you.
Yes, so you can check...
with the stylist if they double-checked her outfit.
- Okay.
- Right.
You're going to wear a bikini?
You're not wearing that?
- I'll take it off later.
- She'll take off her top.
It's quite revealing.
(Her stage performance...)
(is coming up shortly.)
(Goodness)
Since she's wearing her outfit, and she has a performance later,
she fasts.
She doesn't eat until her performance.
So about food...
Shouldn't you at least have some candy?
When did you start fasting?
- I didn't fast per se.
- You ate less.
- I had chicken breasts and eggs.
- Eggs.
- Brown rice.
- I see.
For the last two weeks.
I had things like soy milk noodles.
- For a week?
- Pardon?
- For 2 weeks.
I had a protein-heavy diet.
- For the Waterbomb Festival?
- Yes.
You also ate chicken breasts.
After this ends,
I plan to have Korean beef intestines and spicy chicken feet.
Today?
You can get it delivered.
You can use this card to order.
It's a corporate card.
- Keep it.
- It's a corporate card.
(He acquires a corporate card.)
(With a strange smile, )
(Seo Jin keeps it in his back pocket.)
Why are you keeping it with a suspicious look?
(The caretaker looks weirdly suspicious today.)
(Suspicious dimples)
He kept it like this.
Please help us well with today's event.
- All right.
- Sure.
- Thank you for helping.
Are you going to get some good rest?
(I'm going to get some rest.)
Did you lose some weight?
I didn't lose weight because I gained muscle.
Squats.
(My Star's secret to staying in shape: squats)
Me too.
Since yesterday, I also...
I also started eating less since yesterday.
Don't squat now.
Sit down.
(He casually makes sure My Star saves her energy.)
Don't worry.
I'm really looking forward...
to eating dinner after it all ends.
It's exciting.
(All the best for the Korean beef intestines and spicy chicken feet!)
You don't need to eat anything right now?
Yes, I'm fine.
Seven songs is going to be tough.
(7 songs is going to be tough.)
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Come this way.
(Heading to My Star's waiting room)
- Here.
- It's not cold.
- The AC is turned off.
- I turned it off.
It was cold.
(The AC was turned off for a while because it was cold.)
(He finds BIBI's hand fan.)
(Watching closely)
Your color is purple, right?
- That's right.
- Your signature color.
(Is there anything else?)
Shouldn't we cover her with a towel when it's over?
That's right. When she comes down after it ends...
- We should take it then.
- We should take it.
(The instincts that come with experience)
(What are these clothes?)
What are these clothes?
(What are the strange T-shirts for?)
- What are those for?
They're...
for you to wear.
- For us?
- I...
prepared them.
So,
to get on the stage, you have to take off your shirt.
I think that's why this shirt was chosen.
(Eyes widening)
Will we get on the stage?
Will we be going on stage?
Even if you don't,
- you could try it.
- Well...
BIBI...
might call us...
for something.
(Secretly looking forward to it)
We should wear them since we're told to.
- Wearing it isn't a problem.
- Right.
(I can wear it if I'm told to.)
I shouldn't have eaten.
(Coming soon: Grumpy Secretary's first muscle caretaking)
(Imagining the muscular secretaries)
This is so funny.
(Knocking)
- Yes?
- Hello.
I'm Billlie's manager.
- Pardon?
- Could they come in to greet you?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Come in.
- Hello!
- Hello.
- It's been a while.
- You just came...
straight from your performance.
(They're wet.)
Well done.
Well done. Hello.
Let us greet you. Two, three...
- Belllie've you! Hi, we're Billlie!
(Billlie, the girl group known for their powerful performances)
(Feeling somewhat shy)
I'm sorry, what was the name?
- Billlie.
- We're Billlie.
Okay, I got that.
Nice to meet you.
(The uncle fans are shy.)
They're really huge right now.
They're huge.
- Thank you.
- Really?
- It's an honor.
- All right.
- Nice to meet you.
- They're really...
We're in Producer Yoon Jong Shin's...
- company.
Right.
- MYSTIC?
- They're really hot right now.
Then please tell us...
something bad about Yoon Jong Shin.
- Something bad?
- Yes.
Nice.
- Something bad?
- Yes.
Nice.
He takes care of us really well.
(The rest is omitted.)
To add to that,
- he doesn't keep in touch with us.
- Right.
I think it's been about three years since he said...
- we'd grab a meal together.
- Really?
Producer.
Yoon Jong Shin shouldn't have done that.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Well done.
- Bye.
Bye!
Go eat lots of good food now.
They're always so nice.
They're really nice.
Right.
Did you put those beauty marks under your eye?
Yes.
(My Star's trademark double beauty marks under her eyes)
Did you put them on your nose too?
- These?
- Are those freckles?
That's right. They...
were added by the makeup artist.
(Her beauty marks and freckles were emphasized.)
(He's fascinated.)
- I didn't notice.
- They're there.
(His vision is blurry.)
It's my concept.
What about the other eye?
- What?
- Is that also...
- The makeup artist...
- Did you draw it?
Added it as well.
This looks good.
(She's super excited.)
- She must be really hungry.
- This looks really tasty.
- It'd be okay to eat it.
- Of course.
- Even if you eat it now...
- Eating it now...
isn't suddenly going to make my stomach so...
I'll take them all.
- I'm excited.
- Did the organizers prepare these?
Yes. I can take them.
- I'm taking them.
- Take them all.
- That's my plan.
- Right.
Take the cosmetic products too.
I don't need to take the cosmetic products.
- You don't need to take them?
- Yes.
Could you keep them somewhere?
Do you have a bag?
- You have a bag.
- Right.
I'll have them when we go to the restaurant later.
- Here.
- Thank you.
This...
I really love eating.
Eating is my favorite thing in the world.
I guess...
you're the type who doesn't gain so much weight.
- Me?
- Yes.
- That's not true.
- You gain weight?
- I used to be a CP.
- What's a CP?
A chubby pig.
Really? How much did you weigh at your heaviest?
I...
used to be the heaviest during middle school.
I used to be...
a lot shorter than now.
- I used to be like 155cm tall, - Yes.
And I weighed 66kg.
- You weighed 66kg?
- Yes.
I was quite heavy.
For women, that's quite a lot.
So for my current shape...
I really...
I really worked hard.
But...
I used to be short.
People all lose weight as they get older.
(Sighing)
That looks good.
(She couldn't resist and grabbed a sausage.)
Can you eat sausages?
I'll just eat a little.
- I'm hungry.
- Why don't you...
take something with sugar like jelly instead?
(It will give you energy.)
- Salt is important in the summer.
- What?
- Salt...
Salt...
It makes you swollen?
- isn't good.
- Why?
Salt is the worst thing when you're in a diet.
- Right.
- It makes you swell.
If you need energy...
I should eat something sweet?
Eat a banana instead.
That would make her belly stick out.
- She's...
- She should eat some sugar.
It's better to eat sugar.
(She stops eating after the lecture about salt.)
- We've worked on our bodies before.
- Yes.
Then,
- Did you...
- to get energy...
- ever get your body really defined?
- When I used to do that.
Of course.
Back then...
(Muscular Seo Genie times)
Until the photoshoot,
I would take some chocolate.
(Advice from a former fitness buff secretary)
That's better.
When it's over,
you should eat things like seasoned ribs.
(You should eat seasoned ribs when it's over.)
(Laughing)
Seasoned ribs sound good.
(She loves salty food.)
Naengmyeon.
(Thinking about it makes her even hungrier.)
You can't have them now.
(The sausage she was eating earlier)
(Eating)
Is that the second one or the first one?
It's the first one.
- You're really strict.
- No, I...
I don't nag...
Don't eat things like that.
Take a candy.
It'll give you some energy.
You shouldn't eat salty food when you're on a diet.
- This one? A candy?
- Yes.
Why are you telling me what to do?
- Seo Jin...
- You need to get energy.
You need energy on stage.
- Salt isn't good for your diet.
- It's not good.
- That's true.
- You shouldn't eat...
salty things when you're on a diet.
It's better to eat sugar.
- Yes?
- Excuse me. In two minutes,
please head to her brand booth.
Okay. In two minutes.
My energy is really low.
It's low?
- Pardon?
- Your energy is low?
Yes. My energy is really low because I'm hungry.
Eat the candy quickly.
- I had one.
- No.
- Just eat a whole sausage.
- Eat more.
That's right. One sausage is fine.
(My Star's condition comes first.)
That wouldn't give you energy.
You need something like a banana.
(He may grumble, but he's only worried about My Star.)
- Yes!
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
- Let's go!
- Let's go.
Okay.
(2:35pm, An eyewear brand booth event)
Aren't you wearing glasses?
That's right. I need to wear glasses.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Goodness.
- Aren't there sunglasses?
- Hello.
- Pardon?
- Aren't there sunglasses?
Sunglasses? I'm supposed to wear this one now.
- These ones?
- Yes. These ones.
I can already...
feel my energy drop so much.
How are you going to manage?
You'll get back alive once you're on stage.
- I'll have to endure it.
- Pardon?
I'll endure it.
(Where is Kwang Kyu?)
This is someone else's room.
(He came to get his bag.)
(He doesn't forget to take the water gun.)
Where are they?
Hurry up.
I brought a fan.
Let's go!
(They head outside for the booth event.)
(Greeting)
BIBI! Didn't you see her?
(It's BIBI.)
BIBI!
(Hello)
It's BIBI! She waved at me!
Hello!
(She's showered with her fans' cheers.)
(Laughing)
(My Star is actually...)
(known for her amazing fan service.)
(Kisses for the fans)
(Getting jumpy after seeing her fans)
(Is she the same person who said she was hungry earlier?)
(It's crowded.)
(2:35pm, An eyewear brand booth event)
(Be careful since large crowds may gather.)
(Leading the way to escort My Star...)
This way.
(amid the crowd)
(He even takes care of security.)
(It's reassuring.)
(Kwang Kyu is taking care of her with the handheld fan.)
I was wondering why it felt cool.
I'm your secretary.
Hello. It's been a while.
(They safely arrive at the event booth.)
(Cheering)
You're so pretty!
(She enters the booth to roaring cheers.)
Let's welcome BIBI with a big round...
of applause and cheers!
Please give her a round of applause!
Hello.
(Her fans fill the area in front of the event booth.)
A special event with BIBI.
Are you ready, BIBI?
Who wants to play rock-paper-scissors?
Only those who win will go on.
Those who lose or tie are out.
Get ready!
Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors!
(Paper, rock)
Only those with scissors can continue.
Those with paper and rock are out.
- Congratulations.
- You're so pretty!
Thank you.
What did you say?
She's so pretty!
Yes, you're really pretty, BIBI.
We've given out all the gifts now.
Perhaps...
You know, they're...
some guys I know.
We're not some guys you know. We're your managers.
- That's right.
- We're your managers!
The Grumpy Secretary...
Can they take them?
They came here as BIBI's secretaries.
Try on some that suit you.
- Yes.
- Try on some that suit you.
Kim Kwang Kyu will try them on.
(Let me try on the sunglasses.)
Yes.
(Here it is.)
It suits you well!
Goodness.
It suits you well.
You look like an actor right now.
I am an actor.
(Kim Kwang Kyu, 28 years of acting experience)
And Seo Jin...
(Seo Jin's pick)
They suit him so well.
- Do I look good?
- It's like you're going fishing.
(A look straight out of a fishing trip)
Grumpy Secretary looks handsome!
Please give BIBI another round of applause!
- Thank you.
- See you later!
- Let's move.
Thank you.
(Even on the move, she draws attention.)
- Hello.
- Just follow me.
- I love you, BIBI!
(Leading the way without hesitation)
(She gives her fans plenty of love.)
(2:50pm, moving to the next event booth)
It's the S brand.
(2:55pm, A shampoo brand booth event)
We'll take the photoshoot in the middle first.
Okay.
You'll stand here...
(My Star's favorite shampoo brand's booth event)
(A photo session before the event)
(Going into pro mode)
You're so pretty!
(Everyone falls for BIBI's charms.)
(The crowd came to see BIBI.)
(Everywhere she goes becomes a hotspot.)
Let's go, Lee Seo Jin and Lee Kwang Kyu!
(Kim Kwang Kyu, 28 years of acting experience)
- Lee Seo Jin looks cooler.
- What?
It's really amazing.
Goodness.
(Laughing)
Hello.
You'll meet the manager of the Head and Shoulders brand.
There's a shampoo brand as well.
I don't work with them yet, but I'm aiming for it.
You have to talk to them well.
- The shampoo brand?
- Yes.
- Which shampoo brand?
- I actually...
- Head and Shoulders.
- use the brand's shampoo a lot.
(My Star wants to become a shampoo model.)
(In that case...)
Do you have a model?
- No.
- We don't.
Do you have a model?
- No.
- We don't.
You should use one.
(You should use BIBI.)
This is the truth. I only use your shampoo.
- Really?
- Really.
- Thank you.
(Reading the room)
The shampoo you said you liked earlier?
That's right. I always use it.
The one you've been using.
- For a low fee.
- Right.
We'll give you a good deal.
(He even slips in a little pitch.)
Thank you.
Feel free...
You're the best.
(The Grumpy Secretary is the best!)
Before going on stage,
I refreshed my scalp using Head and Shoulders.
Everyone will be spraying so much water at my performance.
But I'm not worried.
We'll do the ice-breaking challenge last.
Really?
Put on these goggles just to be safe.
We have our own goggles.
Sure.
We didn't bring them. Can't we use these?
- Do what's comfortable for you.
- Okay.
- Wear them...
Okay. Are you ready?
- Yes.
- Give her a round of applause!
(Is he scared?)
One more time!
(Please give me a commercial deal.)
(The first schedule, booth event, is complete.)
(Let's go.)
- Thank you.
- You're so pretty!
(The way back is packed with fans too.)
(Next on My Star's schedule)
It's quite far.
(3:50pm, Waterbomb after-movie photoshoot at the waiting lounge)
The full performance on stage will be shown.
- Yes.
- It'll be shown.
We're going to shoot image cuts to be inserted in between.
(Shooting photos to be included in the performance video)
I'm sleepy.
(She's exhausted.)
(Running on an empty stomach and barely any sleep)
(Blinking)
You have to wear one of the sunglasses.
Right.
Should I wear the goggles or the sunglasses?
They mentioned sunglasses.
That's the one Kwang Kyu wore earlier.
(My Star asked for styling suggestions.)
(How do I look?)
(Carefully checking out today's outfit)
The goggles?
See what's better.
Goggles or sunglasses?
(Sunglasses or goggles?)
(Thinking)
They all look good on you.
(The perfect answer that makes My Star smile)
I think the goggles are better.
Goggles? Okay. I'll go with the goggles.
(Going with the goggles after Seo Jin's firm answer)
(On standby for the image photo shoot)
Ready. Action.
(The look in her eyes changes.)
(Chic)
Very nice.
Perfect.
(Cheerful)
(Hiding her fatigue)
(She's a pro who pulls it off perfectly.)
(Nice)
(The man in charge likes it.)
(Didn't she just say she was tired?)
One more time.
(Despite their worries, My Star looks laidback.)
(In awe)
Very good. One, two, three.
Good. Okay. Cut.
(The best waterbomb queen)
When we zoom in,
can you take the goggles off?
Can you take the goggles off?
(Dashing)
(He's becoming even more perceptive.)
Thank you.
(Smiling)
(Holding the fan with his earnest)
(Cooling himself off too)
You're perfect.
He's a perfect secretary.
You're amazing. Action.
(My Star changes the look in her eyes as soon as it begins.)
(She's a pro.)
Very good.
Thank you. That will do.
- Thank you.
- Let's do it now.
- Let's start the interview.
But I kept...
(Right away?)
- I think it'll be okay.
- Are you doing the interview now?
They're asking for an interview.
(Waterbomb interview in the lounge at 4:10pm)
(There's no break until the performance.)
(Wide open)
If we rush the interview,
you'll have about an hour.
(Getting tired as soon as the shoot ends)
Yes, we have it.
I'm so tired. This is crazy.
Get some sleep after the interview.
I think I should.
(Exhausted)
Crazy.
Hello.
(Keep it up, my girl.)
She must be tired and hungry.
(Worried)
One, two, three.
I'm at the waterbomb.
I'm going to have fun.
I hope you have fun too.
This is BIBI. Isn't it scorching today?
(Pulling off the interview based on her 5 years of experience)
Thank you.
See you later. Bye.
(The end of the interview)
- Thank you. Good job.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
- Wait.
- Hello.
Hello. I'm from here.
We're going to film two.
At first, go, "No pictures."
We'll make three videos.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
(She's tired, )
(but her secretaries make her smile.)
(Giving up on appearing on TV just to serve her)
No pictures.
(Posing)
The last one.
Two.
(Immersed in the concept)
(Didn't she just say no pictures?)
No pictures.
I said, stop it.
Didn't she just say no?
(What is she doing?)
(Understanding the meme belatedly)
What do you think?
(Absurd)
Why is that...
(Trends these days are hard to understand.)
- Good job.
- Thank you.
Let's go. You're done, right?
Are we done?
- There's one more team.
- There's another one?
There are many media.
This is my second waterbomb.
Promise me to cheer as loud as you can.
You have to exercise,
so you won't pass out in hot weather.
Why is this so hard?
Isn't it burning hot?
I'll have fun.
Hello. I'm BIBI.
It's drowning? Are you looking forward to it?
One, two, three. Wink.
Drink protein shake every day.
But don't worry.
Because I'm here.
Have a cool day with me...
It's BIBI at the waterbomb.
Hello...
Thank you. Bye.
That's why she's a pro.
She kept going without hesitation.
She was relaxed.
(She can still afford to smile.)
That's good. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
Let's go now.
Good job, girl.
What do you think?
How does it feel to watch your daughter making money?
It's sad.
And since you're starving...
She was on a severe diet.
(For 2 weeks)
I felt bad for her.
(Feeling bad)
I should be proud of her for being so successful.
If she were his daughter,
he would've spent all her money on himself.
(A short break before the performance)
Sit down. Get some rest.
(Worried)
Rest.
(Recharging with water)
You only have a performance left now.
Yes, I only have a performance left.
(The performance is drawing near.)
Right.
(Feeling tired before the performance)
(Noticing My Star's condition)
Are you tired? Do you want to get some sleep?
Isn't it too cold?
- It's okay.
- What?
- No.
Raise the temperature.
- Take your shoes off.
- Okay.
Take them off.
- They must be sweaty.
(Heavy)
- They feel like...
- Right?
I'm wearing them only because I was told to.
(Seasoned vibe)
Oh, gosh.
Get some rest.
(Finally, resting her legs)
(Kwang Kyu is up to grab something.)
(Rustling)
(A plastic bag?)
- Did you bring slippers?
- Crocs...
(Kwang Kyu's favorite slippers)
Did you bring slippers?
- Did you bring slippers?
- Crocs...
(He helps her wear them.)
Thank you.
(Touched)
- They are...
- They're mine.
(On cloud nine)
I love them.
(My Star loves how comfortable they are.)
- They are...
- They're mine.
(His service has improved.)
(Feeling proud)
(She can't take her eyes off.)
I feel like I've become Cinderella.
Like putting shoes on Cinderella.
It felt worthwhile.
It was a good idea to bring them.
(The Genie makes sure she gets some rest.)
I wore them for like three years.
What if there was gum on it?
I was worried.
Do you always get dirty stuff...
on your shoes?
Yes.
Because...
- I'm kind of worried.
- Why?
I have a philosophy...
about my performance.
What's your philosophy?
(BIBI's performance philosophy?)
Make their money worthwhile.
Just like Seo Jin.
You're a capitalist.
(Capitalism reduces 27 years of age gap.)
Do you like that?
I must entertain those...
who paid to see this.
(My Star with thorough professionalism)
(BIBI's performance is new and hot every time.)
(A stage-dominating performance)
(The singer with 8 years of experience...)
(communicates with the audience.)
(She's ready to make the audience's money worthwhile.)
- That's capitalism.
- It's right.
(While My Star talks about her performance philosophy...)
The air feels stuffy.
(Showtime approaches.)
Raise the temperature.
I'll open the door.
(Warming up her voice due to tension)
(Warming up together to help her relax)
(Eyes on My Star)
(While My Star is getting recharged, )
(the energy on stage is at its peak.)
(The show is getting heated up.)
(BIBI's performance is right around the corner.)
(Until the performance)
Excuse me. You have two minutes left.
Okay. In two minutes.
Keep them on until you leave.
- It's okay.
- Wear them.
I need to practice in them.
- Okay.
- See you later.
Okay.
(But she barely got the rest.)
(My Star is checking the choreography with the dancers.)
(However)
(She suddenly flops down.)
(Due to the tension before the performance...)
(Checking the time)
We should get changed too.
(We should get changed too.)
(Taking off)
I shouldn't have eaten. I'm getting a belly.
Was there a time when you didn't?
But it's too big.
Lately, I'm getting a belly even if I eat only a little.
(Why are the secretaries getting changed before the performance?)
What about the bag?
What?
(Fake abs)
Do we grab our bags?
- Are you leaving your bag here?
- Do I need it?
Are we going now?
People are in a swimsuit,
but we can't.
Honestly, I wanted to take my shirt off.
When I take it off,
my body isn't so bad.
People are surprised.
I just need to lose a bit of a belly.
- First...
- What are you most confident about?
My right chest.
(My right chest.)
Because I'm right-handed.
(Because I'm right-handed.)
Should I?
(Do you want to see it?)
What do you think?
(Feeling danger)
(Genies here to protect My Star with their physiques)
Are you ready? Are you going now?
(In the meantime, My Star returns after checking the choreography.)
(Sighing)
Thank you.
(Still nervous)
Please move to the stage.
Okay. Let's go.
(Moving to the stage without a break)
Let's go.
(Performance in the outdoor global stage at 4:50pm)
(Sighing)
(Trying to calm down by breathing deeply)
(Glancing)
I've prepared it for a long time.
For about 2, 3 months.
(The more effort she put into it, the heavier the burden)
I get nervous when I do it after a while.
But today, I was more nervous than usual.
(Meanwhile, at the stage)
(The audience's energy is exploding.)
(Until the performance)
(Arriving at the standby zone)
I'll help you put the mic on.
(Trembling)
(It's time to go on stage.)
(The pressure is out of control.)
(Feeling bad)
You're not nervous, are you?
I am.
You are?
(She can't easily calm down.)
(Worried)
Be careful when you zip down.
(Okay)
(Trying to calm her down by joking)
You wouldn't slip, right?
(Checking My Star's safety)
It's making me nervous.
It's most nervous before the stage.
I performed...
for 20 days in a row.
Ever since I started working here...
Still, I was nervous before going on stage.
Even though I did it every day.
(Because he's done it, he knows how pressuring it is.)
I was very nervous.
If I do it every day,
I become less and less nervous,
and I'm excited to go up.
But today,
my hands and feet felt cold.
I kept trying to...
wake my body up.
(Until the performance)
(Staring)
- Can you do chin-ups?
- What?
- No.
I thought you could.
I can't.
(Smiling at Kwang Kyu's joke for the first time)
- I can do this.
- When you were hanging,
I thought you were going to do it.
Because I'm nervous.
(Make her laugh by joking.)
(Looking around)
Let's stand in front of the AC.
- It's cool here.
- Yes.
(Make sure My Star isn't hot.)
(Holding the fan for her all day long)
Kwang Kyu...
held the fan...
for me.
He held the fan.
That was touching.
He was very gentle. It was nice of him.
(In sync with My Star)
Now, I'm going to introduce the next artist.
You won't believe it.
(Finally, introducing BIBI's performance)
What is her name?
- BIBI.
One more time. What's her name?
Let's call her out.
Say BIBI.
- BIBI.
(Until the performance)
(Cheering for BIBI)
(Also getting nervous)
BIBI, standby.
- Let's go.
- Go.
(Off to the stage)
(Entering the stage she's prepared for)
- Good luck.
You can do it!
Say BIBI.
- BIBI.
(She can feel the energy behind her.)
Jump, jump!
(Checking the size of the stage first)
(A loud cheer from the audience)
Give it up for BIBI.
(Finally, it's BIBI time.)
Let's go.
(Hey!)
(Until the performance)
- Let's go.
Let's go.
(You got this.)
(It's BIBI!)
(Serving her until the last minute)
(When BIBI appears, )
(people rush in.)
("The Weekend" by BIBI)
(A song about holding on to someone who only comes around on weekends)
(The first Korean female solo singer to reach the Billboard Radio Top 30)
(She completely dominates the stage.)
(The secretaries were watching her behind the stage.)
(Monitoring her performance live)
She doesn't seem nervous.
How does she look to a melodrama's lead role?
If she pulls off this song,
she'll be relaxed.
- You think so?
- Yes.
She doesn't look nervous right now.
(Look how laidback My Star is.)
She's laidback.
Good.
(She completes her first performance successfully.)
Hello, waterbomb.
There are so many of you.
It's awesome.
Thank you for coming.
If you know the next song,
will you sing with me?
- Yes.
(Everyone knows just by hearing the intro.)
("Bam Yang Gang" by BIBI)
(A song about a breakup with a lover who only wanted sincere love)
(Topped the music chart for 4 weeks in a row)
(Kwang Kyu's favorite song)
(The mega hit song loved by all ages and genders)
"Bam Yang Gang."
To hear "Bam Yang Gang" in person,
it was amazing.
Everyone!
- Bam Yang Gang.
(Squealing)
("BUMPA" by BIBI)
(While the performance is going smoothly, )
(the secretaries head out to the audience zone...)
(to watch her in person.)
(The real muscle men spot the fake muscle.)
(They're probably Waterbomb's first fake muscles.)
(Waterbomb tradition: Shooting water guns at people)
(Taken aback by the random water gun blast)
(Welcome!)
Strangers shot water at me.
I was startled.
Is this how young people these days hang out?
We weren't ready at all.
They were wearing swimsuits and such.
- Why didn't you wear one?
- What?
For me to wear swimsuits in public when I'm over 50...
would get me arrested.
(Banning swimsuits himself)
(All eyes are on them, thanks to the fake muscles.)
(A shy counterattack)
(Retreating at the Gen Z-style intense greeting)
No, stop.
(Let's hang out together, secretaries!)
(Secured an umbrella that was on the ground as a shield)
Kwang Kyu, shouldn't we go inside before the water cannon goes off?
The what?
I heard the water cannon goes off.
(Water cannons at "The Weekend" and "She Got It")
Didn't the water cannon go off earlier?
No, it didn't.
- It did just now.
- No, it didn't.
(Completed the 4th song)
(Smiling)
(Back to being an innocent girl as soon as the performance ends)
Hold on.
How about we do a little background check?
Twentysomethings, make some noise!
(I'm also in my 20s!)
(Let me join, please.)
Do you think there are people older than you here?
Do we have people in their 30s here?
Are you ready? Now, 30-somethings, make some noise!
(Make some noise if you're younger than Kwang Kyu!)
Do we, by any chance, have people in their 40s?
Our fabulous 40-somethings.
Do we have 50-somethings here?
(Over here!)
You're in your 60s.
- No, I'm in my 50s.
- No, 60s.
(Kwang Kyu will be in his 60s in 2 years.)
Are there any international fans here?
Great.
I think this might be your favorite song.
Her English is good, right?
Yes. She's better at it than me.
(My Global Star is even good at English.)
Here's "Best Lover."
She didn't ask about the 60-somethings.
("Best Lover" by BIBI)
(BIBI!)
She took her top down.
(Oh, my)
(Watching My Star being in her element in person)
(Taking Waterbomb by storm)
(Dancing)
(If My Star does it, so does the secretary.)
(Immersed)
("She Got It" by BIBI)
(Trying to look calm)
(Staring at nothing)
(The water cannon goes off.)
(Giving off rainy season old-couple vibes)
(Meanwhile, the Waterbombers enjoy it with their whole bodies.)
(The hot performances come one after the other without a break.)
BIBI is a born artist. Yes, she is.
She looked nervous, but when she got on stage,
you couldn't tell at all.
"As expected of a pro."
"She's the real deal."
(Singing her debut song, "BINU," as the last song)
(Engaging with the audience with passion until the very end)
I have a philosophy when it comes to my performances.
"Give them their money's worth!"
"Make sure everyone who paid to be here has an amazing time!"
(BIBI killed this year's Waterbomb!)
(I hope Korea has more unique artists like her.)
(BIBI must know she's charming. She was the Waterbomb Queen!)
Thank you. This was BIBI!
(The Waterbomb Divinity proved herself once again.)
I love you!
See you again!
Oh, my.
(At last, a sigh of relief.)
- Good work.
- Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
- Look at her.
(My Star has a hard time even standing up properly.)
(Her whole body is soaked in sweat and water.)
It's over!
I feel so relieved!
(Seo Genie takes care of My Star without a word.)
You can finally eat as much as you want!
I'm going to grab some grub!
How does it end so quickly when I prepared it for months?
Good luck!
Great job.
Didn't it end really quickly?
It did.
You said you were nervous, but it didn't seem like it at all.
(She's finally laughing.)
You looked so relaxed singing the first song.
- Really?
- Yes, you looked super relaxed.
(Cheering her up with endless compliments)
When I pour my everything out for 30 minutes...
and see people sing along,
do you know how exciting it is?
I know because I released two albums.
Right, you did.
Everyone sings along to Bam Yang Gang.
Yes, and seeing them sing along was...
And that many people too.
I spotted many foreigners today.
Weren't half the audience...
- foreigners?
- Right?
(A rewarding performance after all the hard work)
- Well done.
- Good job.
- You worked hard.
- Be careful.
- We're leaving.
- Dig into lots of delicious food.
It's over!
It's over.
Were you already munching on Homerun Ball?
- Yes.
- Really.
You should fuel up with some good food later, not with snacks.
I won't miss out on the good food either.
By any chance...
What? What is it?
Can you order food for me?
Sure, what kind?
(Genie will order anything.)
We can get delivery there.
Hold on.
Do I have to change the address first?
- I'll do it.
- Give me a second.
(Unable to trust him)
What's the address? What was the name?
Nakasu.
- Na?
- Na.
Na as in N, A.
(Even entering the address isn't easy.)
Nakasu.
(Anxious that he might get it wrong)
Let me check if it's the right place.
Please.
Good.
(Relieved)
Korean beef intestines and spicy chicken feet.
With noodles?
Gosh, it looks good.
- I...
- Crunchy cubed radish?
- Yes.
- Or wrap it radish?
Crunchy cubed radish.
Is there nothing to add?
No.
All right, we're off.
(6:10pm, heading to the wrap-up party place)
- Hold on, Kwang Kyu.
- Okay.
- What is it?
My fans are waiting outside.
Give me a minute.
(The fans are waiting for My Star on her way home.)
Stop.
(Growing impatient)
(The window isn't rolling down.)
- Kwang Kyu, roll down the window.
- Okay.
(Rolling down the window)
The window.
- Stop.
- Okay, stop.
How was it today?
- You're so pretty!
- Oh, my gosh.
What a princess!
I love you all.
Thanks for coming.
Bye.
(Feeling proud of My Star's popularity)
You were good.
- How was the new choreography?
- The choreography...
Was the remix okay?
(My Star's fans spotted the secretaries.)
What does your dad do?
- Thank you. Bye!
- Bye!
(A fan service for My Star's fans)
(Bye!)
- Thank you!
- What does your dad do?
(Excited with BIBI)
You talk to your fans like that?
I'm close with those fans.
They're a year older than me.
- Really?
- Yes.
Shall we get going?
(Leaving the venue and heading to My Star's regular hangout)
I prepared it for months,
but the 30 minutes passed by in a flash.
One song got you relaxed, right?
- Yes.
- Usually...
Yes, and I thought I should get through it.
Before you get on stage to perform,
- you get all nervous.
- True.
But after one song...
I totally agree.
Because of the adrenaline rush, I didn't know I got hurt.
Did you get hurt?
I think her skin got rubbed raw...
- Yes?
- while she was on the floor.
I think so too.
I scraped my elbow but only noticed after getting off stage.
When I went down on the floor.
It was probably during "She Got It."
I think I hurt myself there.
I'm okay. It doesn't hurt that much.
(As expected, My Star is a pro.)
Does it take long to prepare for the Waterbomb?
- The Waterbomb?
- Yes.
It's not a solo concert, is it?
- No, it's not.
- Right?
But do you still prepare for a long time?
I didn't spend all my time preparing just for this,
but I did little by little for a while,
starting about 2 or 3 months ago.
Is that so?
(Prepared the performance for 3 months)
(For the 30-minute performance, )
(practiced for months)
- The songs...
- Yes?
You sing your famous songs...
- every year.
- I do.
Do you need to prepare for it?
Can't you use the old choreography?
That? You see...
The song was remixed,
so even the choreography...
- So it was a remix.
- was renewed.
That's right.
I put a little more effort into preparing for this performance...
as if it were my last one.
- Now...
- No more Waterbombs?
Waterbomb... It's just that...
I don't know if I can do it again.
Losing weight is tough.
Do you have to lose weight?
If I don't, I become a total pig.
That's cute.
As half of the audience is foreigners...
It might work on them.
- They might prefer that.
- True.
(Set to be unleashed at the after-party)
Are you an only child?
- No.
- No?
But I don't get along with my siblings.
Is that so? I guess you don't click.
(Laughing brightly at his friend's family situation)
There's this niece who I really adore.
- Niece?
- Yes.
I only see her.
(Smiling at the thought of his niece)
How old is she? Is she a baby?
She was born in 2003.
She's an adult.
She graduated from college last year and is now living in New York.
(Seo Jin's niece lives in New York.)
- New York?
- My niece also thinks...
New York is the best city.
"If it isn't New York, I can't."
I love Mapo-gu.
I moved to Mapo-gu, and I'm loving it.
Aren't you moving to Mapo-gu soon?
- What?
- Aren't you moving to Mapo-gu?
I thought so too, but the address turned out to be Seodaemun-gu.
- Seodaemun-gu.
Seodaemun-gu is nice too.
(Not great at geography)
Isn't Seochon in Seodaemun-gu?
- No.
- No?
- Is that in Jongno-gu?
- That's Jongno-gu.
- I'm sorry.
- You mean like Bukchon and Seochon?
Yes, Bukchon and Seochon.
- Seochon.
- Yeonhui-dong is in Seodaemun-gu.
- Is Yeonhui-dong in Seodaemun-gu?
- Seodaemun-gu is...
Isn't Sinchon in Seodaemun-gu?
No. Sinchon is in Mapo-gu.
No, Hongdae is in...
- Hongdae is in Mapo-gu.
- Mapo-gu..
Sinchon is in Seodaemun-gu.
- Is that so?
- Let's bet.
- How much?
Okay, I'm in.
What's your say, BIBI?
- Sinchon...
- I say Mapo-gu.
Same here.
Got it.
If I win,
- you give me 50 dollars each.
- Okay.
If I lose,
- I'll give you each 50 dollars.
- Okay.
(Searching right away)
Okay.
(Gasping)
Yonsei-ro, Seodaemun-gu. Okay, 50 dollars each.
- For real?
- It's in Seodaemun-gu.
- What?
- Sinchon is in Seodaemun-gu?
Sinchon is right next to Mapo-gu, but it's in Seodaemun-gu.
- Really?
- May I wire you the money?
(Yes, 100 dollars!)
Is Ahyeon-dong also in Seodaemun-gu?
Ahyeon-dong is in Seodaemun-gu.
(Seo Genie is a genius at geography.)
But how do you know all of that?
Don't people usually only know about their neighborhood?
- You know, Yeonhui-dong...
- Yes?
Two presidents were from that area.
So it's been a famous area for a long time.
People were all about Yeonhui-dong.
Yonsei University used to be Yonhee College.
Yonhee-Severance, right?
It's now Yonsei University,
but it was originally founded as Yonhee College.
Why did it change to Yonsei University?
- That's none of my business.
- Yonhee...
(Confident even when he has no idea)
I think "Yonsei" is short for "Yonhee-Severance."
- Really?
- Yes.
That may make sense.
No, it's a fact.
- Is it?
- Yes.
- Inha University.
- Yes?
Did you also know it's short for Incheon Hawaii University?
- Incheon Hawaii?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Inha University...
is short for Incheon Hawaii University.
Are you serious?
You just came up with it, didn't you?
- No, it's true.
- That's absurd.
I've never heard of that before.
Really, Inha University is short for Incheon Hawaii University.
- Come on.
- It's true!
- No way.
- Come on.
Inha University has no other founding name.
It's simply Inha University.
- Hawaii isn't part of it.
- How much...
How much do you want to bet? Fifty dollars?
A return bet?
- A return bet.
- Good.
I might just walk away with...
fifteen dollars by accident.
(Does "Inha" stand for "Incheon Hawaii University?")
Inha University.
(Searching Inha University)
I'm right.
"The name 'Inha' of Inha University comes from..."
"the first syllable of Incheon and the first syllable of Hawaii."
"Inha University was founded in Incheon in 1954 with donations..."
"from Korean immigrants in Hawaii,"
"commemorating the 50th anniversary of Korean immigration..."
"and supporting..."
- "Korea's industrial development." - Listen.
That was how it was founded, and it was named Inha University...
- Is that so?
- from the start.
It didn't have a founding name of Incheon Hawaii University.
Come on.
- Incheon...
- That's basically the same thing.
The name is from...
the first syllables of Incheon and Hawaii, so she's right.
(Pouting out of fluster)
Give it back.
- Give it back!
- Give it back.
Inha University started off as Inha Engineering College.
- Seriously, how annoying.
- Either way, no Incheon or Hawaii.
- Guess what Ajou University is.
- What?
Guess what Ajou University is.
Ajou...
It stands for "Asia State University."
- For real?
- Yes.
Do you want to lose all your fortune?
No, it's true.
- It's all written here.
- Do you want to lose...
all your fortune?
- It's all on here.
- Really.
Here, if you search up Asia State University...
It was founded as Ajou Technical Junior College...
- Really, how annoying.
- and later became Ajou University.
- You're a handful.
- I found nothing about it...
being called Asia State University.
I'm only reading Wikipedia.
Wikipedia.
Anyone can write on it.
You shouldn't trust it.
With Inha and Ajou, you owe me 150 dollars.
Come on, I'm right. Stop being stubborn.
Yes, just say that she's right.
- Seo Jin, you're a little...
- Yes?
I don't know how to put it into words,
but you're hateful, very hateful.
I hear that a lot.
- You do?
- Gosh.
How hateful.
Either way, you owe me 50 dollars.
Can I get a cash receipt?
Of course not.
(BIBI may have lost money, )
- We're in the hot Yeonnam-dong.
- Yeonnam-dong.
(but she's getting close to her food!)
It looks good.
(My Star's Schedule:)
(7:05pm, BIBI's Yeonnam-dong regular spot for an after-party)
(The food has been delivered.)
(Received by Lee Seo Jin)
(Reuniting with spicy chicken feet after 2 weeks)
Hi.
Oh, my gosh.
What... Look around.
I'm going to dig in first. I'm starving.
Go ahead. Dig in.
(Frantically moving hands)
(Overjoyed to finally meet her favorite food)
(Opening)
What is that? Tteokbokki?
- No, chicken feet.
- Chicken feet.
(My Star's mind was filled with thoughts of chicken feet.)
(Finally tasting the earthly indulgence after 2 weeks)
Could we get more plates?
- Sure.
- A big plate.
(Uneasy)
I'm... Thank you for the food.
- Dig in.
- Okay.
(It's finally time to taste the long-awaited chicken feet.)
(Amazed)
The last time I had something saucy...
It's been a while, right?
Was about two weeks ago.
Goodness.
(It's delicious!)
I'll pour out the juice.
(My Star's reward for 2 weeks of patience)
- For two weeks.
- You also ate chicken breasts.
Chicken breasts and soymilk noodles.
I'm really looking forward...
to eating dinner after it all ends. It's exciting.
That looks good.
My energy is really low.
Yes. My energy is really low because I'm hungry.
She must be really hungry.
(In bliss)
(Eating the beef intestine)
(It's so good that she can't help but dance.)
(Staring)
You must want rice. Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Should I have ordered some rice?
(They want her to enjoy it to the fullest today.)
It's okay.
Eat slowly.
Have it with that.
- It's spicy.
- Okay.
(Finally trying some food)
Try it.
- It's boneless, right?
- Yes.
- Is this the beef intestine?
- I love offal.
- What?
Offal.
Offal. You know, innards.
I'm not a fan of offal.
You can't eat it at all.
I used to be something like a vegetarian in the past.
- Really?
- Slightly, yes.
- I...
- He's lying.
(Nonsense)
- Stop lying.
- No, for real.
I couldn't eat meat at all.
(Kwang Kyu was far from a meat lover.)
The fact that you were a vegetarian is a shocker.
He's lying.
It's a lie, okay?
He digs into pork belly like mad.
(The white lies are back.)
I'm full.
- Full?
- You barely touched it.
She's full after barely touching the food.
- Do you need napkins?
- Thank you.
(Taking care of her in between)
I'll wire you the money once you give me your number.
Don't worry about it.
(A full stomach brings back the bet from the car)
How much will you send me?
Fifty dollars.
Are you just ignoring the other two?
I'm not. I stated the facts, okay?
(A little scared)
It's actually Incheon Hawaii University!
You know.
This feels like a fight with a kid.
I get it.
Give me a minute. Let me ask my cousin.
- Call your cousin.
- I'll call her.
- Did she attend that school?
- Yes.
- Which school? Inha University?
I'm sure I have a friend who graduated from Inha University.
- Inha University...
- There's Kim Gu Ra.
Ask Kim Gu Ra.
(Calling in all possible connections)
- Hey.
- What's up?
I explained that Inha University stands for...
"Incheon Hawaii University," but no one believed me.
- But you're right.
- Right?
(She's right?)
I entered Inha University in 2016.
Inha University does stand for "Incheon Hawaii University."
(The Inha University graduate sets the record straight.)
- These people are driving me crazy.
- Is everything okay now?
(Laughing)
They kept saying I was wrong.
You got it right.
- Right? Thanks.
- No problem.
- Bye.
- Thanks.
(My Star is back to smiling.)
(I was right, wasn't I?)
- Right. Even a graduate said so.
- Listen.
I'll accept it if even Kim Gu Ra says it's true.
(You want another phone call?)
If another graduate says it's true,
I'll accept it.
(Extremely childish)
Our conversations today...
should be about the Waterbomb or BIBI...
Can't you just check with him?
- Hurry up.
- Please.
(Most curious about the truth behind Inha University)
- Hurry up and call him.
- Please.
Fine. Goodness.
- Hello?
- Hey.
- Are you busy?
- No, it's fine.
- Are you free for a call?
- Yes.
Listen.
You graduated from Inha University, right?
Yes, I did.
Does Inha University stand for Incheon Hawaii University?
Does it stand for Incheon Hawaii University?
It does.
- It does?
- Yes.
It does.
(My Star was right!)
- Seriously?
- As far as I know,
- it started in the 1950s...
- Yes?
With donations from first-generation Korean immigrants...
from Hawaii who were living in Incheon...
at the time. Why the question?
- So the name...
- Incheon Hawaii,
hence Inha.
Incheon Hawaii, hence Inha University.
Correct.
That's how you know it as, right?
No, it's the truth.
(Feeling much better)
We're in the middle of shooting My Genie Secretary.
- Thank you, Gu Ra.
- No worries.
Thank you very much.
It's basic knowledge, you know?
(It's basic knowledge, you know?)
Because we wouldn't believe her,
it was only right for her to be infuriated.
Inha University...
stands for Incheon Hawaii University?
I never knew.
What about Ajou University?
- Who do we ask?
- Asia State University?
I know someone who graduated from Ajou University.
Jee Seok Jin graduated from Ajou University.
- Is that so?
- He graduated from Ajou University.
How do you know everyone's university?
He mentioned it the last time...
- we were shooting.
- Did he?
- Hello?
- Seok Jin.
- Pardon?
- Seok Jin?
- He said, "Pardon?" - Who is this?
(Puzzled)
- Hello?
- Seok Jin.
- Pardon?
- Seok Jin?
- He said, "Pardon?" - Who is this?
(Puzzled)
It's me, Kwang Kyu.
Hey.
I lost your phone number.
(Phone numbers expose their true level of closeness)
What's up?
- I've got a question for you.
- Kwang Kyu.
You graduated from Ajou University, right?
Yes.
I want to know something about Ajou University.
What show is this for?
My Genie Secretary.
It's going on again?
Yes.
Congratulations.
Hi, Seok Jin.
- Hey, who is this?
- It's Seo Jin.
Hi, Seo Jin.
- Our Celebrity Lee.
- Hi.
You see,
- we're having...
- Ajou University?
A little dispute about Ajou University.
What about it? What about Ajou University?
BIBI is our guest.
- She said Ajou University...
- Yes?
Stands for Asia State University.
We kept telling her that it was nonsense.
Ultimately,
you came to mind as you graduated from Ajou University.
We joked around with people who didn't know,
saying it was Asia State University.
(We joked around.)
We joked around.
(Frozen in place)
Was it a joke?
You're joking, right?
We joked around, saying it was Asia State University.
(Laughing brightly)
- Thank you.
- No problem.
I'll call you again.
- Hi, BIBI.
- Hi.
Kwang Kyu.
Yes?
- Don't treat me like...
- Yes?
I'm older in a public setting.
(Don't treat me like I'm older in a public setting.)
Sir.
Congratulations on turning 60, sir.
- Take care.
- Congratulations.
Thanks.
- Thank you, sir.
- Bye.
(Feeling bad for some reason)
Food has made me...
- Sleepy?
- You're sleepy, right?
- sleepy.
- Of course.
- Remember how I had Homerun Ball?
- Yes.
My blood sugar level has spiked.
Did you go on a diet for two weeks...
- for today's Waterbomb?
- Yes.
Two weeks?
- Just for this one very day?
Amazing.
I asked my company to book me...
for the Waterbomb Festival to sing...
- "Open Sesame." - You asked for too much.
I was going to sing it as "Open Waterbomb."
Don't you think it's better...
to sing alone in the bathroom?
After watching it,
I really want to perform now.
It was super cool.
Those who come to the Waterbomb Festival are...
ready to have some fun.
(Let's go!)
They go with the flow,
matching the energy.
So as not to disappoint the audience who paid to be there.
I have to show the audience everything I can.
Capitalism.
I'll tell you when you come by my house.
Can we drop by your house?
Of course.
Someone who confidently carves...
her own path in life.
Someone who keeps moving in the direction she wants,
no matter what anyone else says.
BIBI is like that.
The queen of "Bam Yang Gang."
I was so happy to have met my Cinderella today.
It's such a relief that her performance...
ended smoothly...
without any problems.
The best moment was when Seo Jin...
wrapped me with a towel.
It gave me the relief that it was over.
He was so kind to me, which made me happy.
Good job, everyone. Thank you for today.
- Well done, My Star.
- Good job.
(A surprise visit to My Genie Secretary)
(My Star Cha Tae Hyun)
How do I pay my part-time managers?
- How do I pay you?
- Part-time pay?
(First paycheck ever in My Genie Secretary?)
Long-distance trips, late nights, and weekend duty.
It came to a little over 200 dollars.
(Give us more.)
(And so...)
(Genie will do anything for the paycheck.)
(From guiding the way around the venue)
(Serving up a meal enthusiastically)
(Making sure there's warm barley tea for the sick My Star)
(Things were going well.)
(But Kwang Kyu loses focus?)
Kwang Kyu.
She's going to catch my cold.
(I'll set things right!)
(Sorry, I'll get a grip.)
(Secure the lost paycheck)
Ten dollars!
Isn't he the first to pay us?
(Capitalism is the best!)
(And My Star's passion-filled performance)
(I love you.)
(A medley of hit songs that gets the crowd singing along)
(It's the 1st day of My Genie Secretary.)
It's the first day!
(My Genie Secretary)